AYUSH JAMES

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER



linkedin.com/in/ayushjames



github.com/iwishjames



ayushpjames@gmail.com



0401 379 011

PROFILE

I am a Junior Developer who is committed to creating tasteful web applications, by considering the experience of the users, and the objectives of the product - form and function.

I believe my educational and employment experiences enable me to meet the demand for developers with both technical knowledge and business acumen.

I take pride in knowing that that a career in software best positions me to make a valuable contribution to humanity's technological advancements. I am excited for what is to come!

TOOLS

HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, JQUERY, RUBY, SINATRA, RAILS, AJAX, UNDERSCORE, GIT REACT, NODE

EDUCATION

Software Engineering Immersive 2019 General Assembly, Sydney

Bachelor of Commerce (Accounting) 2017 University of Wollongong

RECENT PROJECTS

Locus - Sydney suburb guide

RAILS, GOOGLE API, JAVASCRIPT

A centralised guide for renters that provides a breakdown of the property market in Sydney. github.com/lpinzari/project-suburb

XP - GA student forum

RAILS, DATABASES, BOOTSTRAP, HEROKU

A community forum and knowledge base consisting of tips and experiences shared from the General Assembly. github.com/iwishjames/project1

Tic Tac Toe - Simple kids game

HTML, JAVASCRIPT, CSS, GITHUB PAGES

Your standard game of tic-tac-toe, but with the ability to undo a player's move! The game also utilises Apple's Animojis. github.com/iwishjames/tick_tac_toe

EXPERIENCE

AR Media

Mar 2019 - Current

Creative (Volunteer)

Role: Applying creative approaches to marketing and presenting media content.

Transferable Skills: Marketing strategy, social marketing,

Publift (AdTech)

Sep 2018 - Jun 2019

Accounts Manager (Full-time)

Role: Ad revenue processing and management

Transferable Skills: Business acumen, technical mindset, user experience, project management,

Deloitte (Assurance Advisory)

Apr 2018 - Sep 2019

Junior Analyst (Full-time)

Role: Big-4 bank remediation project.

Transferable Skills: Team collaboration, task management.

Prime Partners (Business Advisory) Nov 2017 - Apr 2018

Graduate Accountant (Full-time)

Role: Assisting with tax and business advisory for individuals. **Transferable Skills:** Process documentation, emotional

intelligence.